Mohamed Ibrahim Abdulghani

Back-End Developer

Experienced PHP developer with extensive server-side web development knowledge gathered across 2 years in the industry. Well-versed in Front-End development. Led company-wide integration with third-party APIs. Seeking to broaden knowledge of databases and deliver the highest standards of web design.











Work Experience

Back-End Developer • Freelancer

I create the database and connect to it through PHP code and combine it with the front-end codes that help create a practical and smooth experience for the end user and make the site dynamic

October 2022 - Present

Front-End Developer • QP Company

I have experience as Front End Developer I have delivered a lot of Web pages

July 2020 - March 2022

Education



2018 - 2022

Cairo Higher Institute for Engineering, **Computer Science and Management**

Graduation Project Assessment Is (A+)

Skills

- PHP
- MySQL
- Laravel
- HTML5
- CSS3
- JavaScript
- Bootstrap
- JQuery
- Angular
- Typescript
- Git

Languages

- Arabic Native
- English Intermediate